# Jingshu (Nora) Sun

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER

**(** 0414 896 688

is.s@live.com

github.com/jssnora

im linkedin.com/in/jssnora

mora-sun.netlify.app

# ABOUT ME

Full-stack developer. Recent Software Engineering Bootcamp graduate. Passionate problem solver with an inquisitive mind. Driven by the need to understand the 'why' and always be learning. Over 5 years experience in the financial services industry.

## SKILLS

LANGUAGES

Javascript | Ruby | HTML | CSS | SQL |

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

Ruby on Rails | SASS | Bootstrap | React | Node | Express |

**TESTING** 

Jest | RSpec | Postman |

OTHER TECHNICAL

TDD | Git | Agile |

#### **PROFESSIONAL**

Problem solving | Critical thinking | Quick learner | Communication | Creativity | Detail Oriented | Teamwork |

# KEY PROJECTS

# Full Stack App for a Travel Business

- Online platform facilitating the sale of packages and products
- Admin functionality to manage products, orders and users
- React frontend, Node, Express & MongoDB backend
- https://tasmania-resort.netlify.app

#### eCommerce Platform

- Online marketplace for buying and selling homemade baked goods
- Developed with Ruby, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Stripe, Amazon S3, Bootstrap and hosted on Heroku
- https://crumbl.herokuapp.com

# **CLI Weather App**

- A CLI application that allows the user to view today's weather or a 7 day forecast of a selected Australian city
- Developed with Ruby using the OpenWeatherMap API
- https://github.com/jssnora/Terminal-App

# **EDUCATION**

# Diploma of IT

(Web Development Bootcamp)

Coder Academy

2021 - 2022

## **Bachelor of Commerce**

(Major in Actuarial Studies)

University of Melbourne

2012 - 2015

## PREVIOUS WORK EXPERIENCE

## Remediation Analyst

2020 - 2022

- Investigate client issues in the remediation process
- Communicate with internal and external stake holders including case escalations

# Financial Paraplanner

2016 - 2020

- Develop financial strategies alongside Financial Planners in areas such as managed funds, tax and superannuation
- Prepare legally compliant & accurate Statement of Advice documents via Xplan
- Training new staff on processes & products